Contact

lilianarcovaliu@yahoo.com 832-720-2256 (Mobile) lilianarcovaliu@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lilianac-2647ba23 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Electronic Medical Record (EMR) Healthcare

Certifications

CMSRN

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

NIH stroke certification

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Publications

Nightingale Society recipient

LILIANA COVALIU

CHARGE RN III, BSN, CMSRN

Spring, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled Charge Nurse, Preceptor, Microsoft Word, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), worked for 22 years in acute patient care hospital setting and outpatient setting. Strong healthcare experience, a professional registered nurse with a BSN focused in Nursing Science from Grand Canyon University and currently enrolled in the Master's program in Nursing with an emphasis on Leadership.

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health Charge RN III, CMSRN, BSN 2012 - Present (8 years)

The Woodlands

NorthShore University HealthSystem 7 years 1 month

Clinical Nurse Manager/ Family Practice office June 2011 - June 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Gleview / Illinois

Charge Nurse

June 2005 - June 2011 (6 years 1 month)

Glenview, Illinois

Our Lady of the Resurrection Medical Center Nurse Extern

January 2001 - February 2005 (4 years 2 months)

Chicago, Illinois

Education

Grand Canyon University

Master of Nursing, Nursing Leadership -Currently enrroled · (2019 - 2020)

Grand Canyon University

BSN, Nursing Science · (2018 - 2019)

SPSB ARAD

Nursing · (1994 - 1997)